taxindiaonline.com 2018-08-15

# TIOL - Tax News, GST, Income Tax, Service Tax, Customs, Central Excise, International Taxation, Fiscal Policy, Monetary Policy, Economy, Revenue, Judicial Decisions, Tax Rulings & Tax Video

Untitled Document

**PRIVACY POLICY**

TIOL group of websites respect the privacy of their audience and considers it as one of the prime concerns of its organisation. TIOL and its group websites do not collect personal information of anyone who visits the website(s) unless the user consents to provide his/her information.

TIOL website(s) only collect the requisite personally identifiable information that helps it serve its subscribers in offering customized services. Personally identifiable information includes, but is not limited to, first and last name, physical address, e-mail address, phone number, birth date, and any other information that itself identifies or when tied to the above information, may identify an user as a specific individual. 

TIOL website(s) do not collect personally identifiable information about its user except when the user specifically and knowingly provides it. TIOL website(s) use personally identifiable information to operate the sites and services and to inform the user of new features and services. The collected and stored information of the users are never meant to be sold to any third-party entiry or intended to be used by TIOL website(s) for any other purpose than as specifically mentioned in this paragraph.

TIOL website(s) handles the user data securely, including transmitting them using modern cryptography (e.g. over HTTPS).

**Information automatically collected/stored**

The kind of information that is gathered automatically include browser type of the user (e.g. Firefox, Safari, Internet Explorer, etc), the Operating System type (e.g. Microsoft Windows, Mac OS, etc.) and the domain name of the Internet Service Provider (e.g. Airtel, Vodafone, VSNL, MTNL, etc.), the date and time of visit and the pages visited. 

**Collection of information by third-party websites**

TIOL website(s) may contain links to other websites whose privacy policies may be different to TIOL's. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as TIOL website(s) has no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

TIOL website(s) use third party like Google and other companies of repute to serve advertisements. While serving advertisements, the third-party advertiser may place or recognise a unique "cookie" on the user's browser and may use information (not including name, address, e-mail address) about the users' visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to the user.

**Other websites links on TIOL website(s)**

TIOL website(s) also has links to other website(s). The privacy policies of such website(s) is not under TIOL's control. Once a user leaves TIOL website(s), use of any information provided by a user is governed by the privacy policy of the websites being visited. It is advisable to read their privacy policies for further information.
